The film will come to dissuaded the
principle now, or this idea
once, things in the universe. Generally, it
's difficult the way they are talked about, forced
in time. Generally, on time, they explain
their causes, and they rely
on comparisons of one to another,
or they all appear
suddenly. Nothing more is formed
beyond mental images and
names. This idea may never have been
legally related to
any single object in the
world. If we think like that, we
approach the view that things that exist with
reality are that, together we will
have to assert
that there is not a single thing in
this entire universe that depends on
conditions, and then we will
have to go further and say that nothing
exists at all.
It's very difficult, U21, it's difficult,
this death, it's very difficult, but
on the day of meditation, the Lama said that
we will consider the idea, together we have to
approach this world, the
first thing we like is what,
or to say that everything, the way
What everyone says is exactly right.
Let's say the way you see the
internet, or when you're on the internet
reading the news,
try to see if all of that is
accurate.
And the logic is that everything that happens is
due to economic reasons,
business, political figures,
things
related to health in the world,
all those events and all
those pressures
in the world, politics, economics,
health. All of those things push
everything, push everything,
and how everything in this world
happens.
And not only that, but
happiness itself is
real if you feel it. For example, if your
friends are stuck in your house
after a year because of this virus,
it's very strange when you can go
out, go to a coffee shop in Sedna,
and they say they'll
close at 5 pm, but people
close at 1 pm. Last week they even
closed at half-hours.  Below, not yet. But, but if,
and compared, instead of
sitting at home all day, or
going out and letting the
coffee shops close at noon,
going out is still interesting.
Before noon,
when we compare the world, we say there are
two possibilities. First, the
internet, news,
everything. Download things about politics, all
the things that the season says, all the
forces in this world
about economics, politics, the
health situation, all these things cause
everything. And
if you feel happy or not, it's
simply by
comparing. It's like wishing COVID-19
a coffee shop in Sedona is one of
the places where a person is the best in the
world, but
after COVID-19, it seems like it's a
very interesting place.
Everything is placed. See the
comparison. That's how this world
was discussed and talked about in the
first month. Now,
this is the second possibility.
Everything simply happens when the
image comes from the  Your imported seed,
this is how everything happens.
Forget about subtlety, forget about politics.
Forget about healthcare. There is no
force in
this world pushing each other and
creating happiness or
sadness or a group of people. All of
these things don't exist. The
second possibility is that
everything we see,
even the big things like what
11 countries are doing,
comes from my own living seed. I am my
personal living seed.
I am
looking at the world, the story of that thing,
because the seed, like the images, comes from
within, from the images in my mind.
Now, for example, I have a picture of a
very delicious glass of lemonade, or here,
watermelon juice. Sorry, I'm going to the store.
Like my friend
Christina, it's hard to go to the store. They
can buy a watermelon.
They ask to bring it to the academy for her. I bring it
home. How can I do that?
I can make that glass of water.
This is how I made it cry
again, it's bad. This is the first and the
second, the second possibility is that I shared
my food, she shared the finished old, I
have my country with
poor countries, and I helped the
new poor countries, I built houses in
Vietnam for you, Binh, for the
poor in Vietnam. The second is that I helped the project
of the teacher, Pretty, to recruit
poor people around the world to be
able to make big machines, old books, or
I put a seed in
my mind to get
this watermelon water. Suddenly, this morning it bloomed,
and this watermelon water container
filled my hair. I can drink
this deep water
here. Saying that on day 3, he silently
said that, for example,
this watermelon water, it bloomed suddenly,
and see if they don't plant
watermelons, and Christina or the inflammation, they don't
bring watermelon results, this academy or
old, and La didn't drive there, and then,
miss, that kind of house is
n't  That's how I
got the cup with the watermelon result,
letting it bloom. It sprouted according to my living seed.
Here,
there are names,
the roles of these
names, what are they? I understand.
When the teacher taught about the hot seed
in my mind, I understood that the time
was teaching about the seed catching it, it falling, and then it bloomed,
and an image appeared
afterwards. Then, on that day, it started to have
color and shape, and that image
created this watermelon juice, the
red color, and in this rapid image, I
understand. But why is there a
name here? Why is there a name here? Why?
The picture, that picture, must have
a name, a title. It's
a bit confusing, it's not just words;
it appears in your mind
and creates everything. When I say that
in the ways, on the
Middle Way, from
the day of the Lama meditation here, on the infinitely infinite day,
what remains is human,
not the path. The
Middle Way of this book
is one of  The most beautiful books
on that high Middle Way, and
seeing the scholar, why talk about
titles or names? Understanding the image,
but is it really necessary to have
a title or a name? Even
a neighbor remains in my
mind through
helping
the poor in the world, and
the image emerges from the
seed, and then it creates
this cup, creates a cup of wine.
The boy cries for me, needing a
name. Why are we continuous
on that Middle Way?
Why ask if it's not continuous? They say
it's just a title, it's just a name. It's just a name, this name is a title
for the image, the title, the name, it's just something, something for a name,
for an image,
everything, it's not. I don't know what title, that name, that name, it's
just images, it's not
candy, the sound of that name,
and it's not something that's
spelled, spelled the same thing.  The name
we give in this world, when
the paths on the Middle Way say that
everything that happens
means everything comes from
images in your mind. When you have a word, that
word is a name, it will be a symbol or
an echo for that image.
My seed today has bloomed into a
small image that appears and it
creates a red color, then the cup is better than
us
when I say to Osasuna, scared, no matter
who is here. Yes, what is in
this cup?
You know,
I don't want to say it's a rubber man.
I have a mental image, a
red liquid.
I will use a nickname,
a short name called Minh Minh.
I say it's watermelon juice. Then, if
in Osasuna, there is an equal woman
in the box, I want to say that there is
an image that appears in the
seeds, about a substance, a
cup of red water that tastes good, and
I call it watermelon juice. It sounds
because...  Because when I ask, when my question
is, I, I drink an
image with a mouth, a sweet
red taste, it jumps out and appears from
within my karma, so let's
use words
to talk about that image, then there's
something that happens, we forget that it's
just a name,
we think, "Me? Really?" We think
that's right, enemy, enemy, enemy,
attack, attack, I attack, I fight,
no, I hate, I hate, I
use a name
and we start. We forget
that there's an image
behind the name, it goes down to the ground, then
we believe that name, then
we get out of the line and call everyone's name.
Oh, you're so stupid. You're so
terrible. You don't like me.
Then we get stuck behind those names, I, it's
here. He says who's watching
who's talking. Here, she or
he, who's here?
Today
we're very lucky because you,
interesting angel.  And I'm saying, "
I'm checking your mind to see if
you're inviting the devils to
talk to you." Or maybe I'm calculating that
in this part, the devils
might be busy with their phones and
not talking much in
this part we're learning. Maybe
next time they'll come,
we'll try to learn the part about angels
and devils. About once every few months,
when we have time,
we can happily
read that together. When we
can gather
in the angel's head and say, "Look,
this world isn't the result
of
external economic or political forces, or
things that appear and push
from within your mind. It
's not this way, and it's not
that way either." In
American English, it means we can
have it both ways, but we have to choose. You ca
n't have both, you have to
choose only one is right, or
nature rules the world.
Or is it an economic power, a
political power, like Tong Thi Nhu?
It's either real or an image
that emerges from your living seed,
it depends on how you treat
others, and the previous guy or last year,
right? But the angel says,
look, we can't have it
both ways. And I'm not
just talking about the world, I'm talking about
your delicious food,
and I'm also talking about the tip of your nose,
everything, everything,
I'm talking about the lion that will be in its
form,
everything comes from
your mind or nothing at all. It's
the person, the intention,
and if you decide
that there is an atom in
your life that is not your fault, if
you decide to
discard
an atom that is
not your fault, then nothing
arises from cause and effect. If there is a
person in this world
who doesn't come from your side,
then nothing comes from your side.
If nothing comes from your side,
then you have to say that nothing
exists, I have nothing.
You have to choose, you have to choose
for
everything that happens to you. It
comes from the way you treat
others, or nothing happens to
you. It depends on how you treat
others. You can't have
both ways. If you
decide that everything that happens
in your life is not
your fault, then nothing can exist
in this world, in
this universe. You understand, sir?
And another victim.
I like you. People come from doing things. Some people
are kind. Can you read this?
On, on, get, and attempted is up from their
public. Now, my point of view
on all of this is that everything that exists
comes from the fishbowl of
causes and conditions and things that depend
on laws. Then we
can say that everything that
exists is karma and
its results are  Something we truly
experience, and if you stick with me,
you can keep your ideas about
spiritual effects and
spiritual paths, and the Three Jewels
in my camp. They all exist
in their names, but they are
there, the names
we take as expressions. Existence
in reality, the path. You want
us to go, then nothing in
this universe can always exist
outside. Steve Gleason
wishes this guy could, I could speak
Vietnamese. I know it's very
difficult to see a
product that her. Here, someone says, "Do
you want to
know my status?" Who said that?
Yes, an angel. You are talking.
Do you know her? Do you want to know me? What am I saying?
Tell me what you are
saying. Everything comes from cause and effect.
Everything comes from cause and effect.
Never forget this,
never forget when the angel says, "
Everything comes from causes and
conditions. Everything is cause and effect, cause and effect."
What does cause and effect mean? Being
kind to others is simple, that's all.
Don't overcomplicate things; everything will naturally fall into place.
What is cause and effect?
What is karmic retribution? It's simply
about how you treat
others, whether you are realistic
or not. Because that's how it is, and
it comes from how you treat others. Forget about
this big world, let's move on.
The way you do things, the karmic retribution, it's
simple, it just means how you
treat others and whether you
treat people kindly or not. That
's cause and effect,
and karmic retribution. Here, it means two things. Look,
I support my vote. It's just
cause and effect. The origin of
everything comes from how we
treat others.
If you agree
that everything in your life
jumps out from the seed of life
that you have sown from being
kind or treating others badly,
if you agree with that,
then everything you want will be
smooth sailing. If you don't
agree...  With a seed, everything is
nothing,
right? It's so cute.
If you believe in the seed,
then everything is 94 times it is. If
you don't believe in the seed,
then everything that exists isn't nonexistent. It doesn't
exist,
right?
Now, in the movie "Angels," they say
something very lovely, saying, "
Stay with me, stay by my side,
stay with me, and you will have a
good life.
Don't listen to those foolish people.
If you
still believe in the seed as I said, oh,
then you can enter the five paths of
Buddhahood, or you can enter the ten
lower levels of Bodhisattva practice. Only when you believe in the
seed can you have the
Dharma, the Sangha. And if you don't
believe in the seed,
you can't have the Three Jewels.
And if you don't have the Three Jewels, you ca
n't be a molecule, you can't be.
That's the
definition of a person.  If you're a Buddhist, then when
you accept the idea of ​​living a humble life,
when you accept the
idea with these angels that the
world comes from your side, then you,
young, can practice Buddhism.
But don't forget, you're a
captain who once praised me for
running, so it means if you agree, yes,
my point of view, what I'm saying, if
you agree with the whole topic about everything, there are
Bodhisattvas there, I
can say, can see the knowledge,
I
can worship the Buddha, Dharma, and Sangha, how is it only
when you understand that everything
comes from your side, only when
you understand that everything is good,
your life when you can
practice Buddhism on your own, there is no punishment
that is not good, your expectations,
there are no immutable classes with microphones
off that cost you money, there
is
no saying, the Sangha, you have to find a way to
build, and it doesn't come from
your side,
she doesn't  There are other types of vegetables
or Yes. Everything is one hundred percent
to your practice or zero
percent on your side, there is no
compromise whatsoever.
Negotiate here, there is no one percent, no zero percent,
it is not from
your vote, and this means
you cannot hate anyone, not even
one percent.
Everyone is your fault.
All the people who want to talk,
then this is the dark head of your vote. There is
a joke at the Diamond Study Abroad Center, at the
Diamond Road Center, all the
staff are very well trained, and
many of them set up very
useful courses. They are people who are
very well trained, and they all
understand
now
when they meet someone like a fool. It is
expected that there must be jokes
at the Diamond Study Abroad Center, each person one person, they
say, "I can't believe it, I can't
believe it, that all
these people are right, right? You are right, you are
right, you are right. You are right,
there is a level of taking, which means that all
Everyone in your organization, if
everyone loses, everyone
around you is stupid.
If both of your family members do
n't understand anything
and you criticize them, you
're only criticizing
yourself. Speaking of which,
we'll go through another ordeal. In there,
we'll contribute to the Q&A,
predictions for South Africa,
and a real,
weird sword.
A
happy to see
you are the past, darkness. You're
misunderstanding, and your statement that everything that
exists in reality
is a misunderstanding. That leads to the idea
that nothing can exist, not even
by name. Misunderstanding is
worse than misunderstanding. You are the entire
giant planet of all ignorance.
This is a suffering realm, very
unpleasant, isn't it?
Usually, angels don't say
bad things, not even to the devil,
but here, in this version, the angel says that you
are darkness, you are darkness, and darkness.
Meaning when
you can have the entire world
of an economy.  Success is achieved
through intelligent people,
but without laws.
If no one, even you, have technology,
you have the internet,
you have airplanes.
You can send missiles
to the moon every day. But if you don't
understand the seed,
you're living in a world where you
see low-level people
saying, "We're not
cavemen, we don't live
in caves, we don't fight, we don't
throw stones, we don't kill
people, we don't eat
food." Well, even cars are used for food. We are
civilized people, meaning
cultured people, and what are we?
We have technology.
This is the first time
in
50,500 that I can have a meeting point
across the world, and there are
people from South Africa, people
from Vietnam,
and people from Germany,
all coming together every year. This is
a wonderful and sincere world, but it's
not just darkness.
It's worse than the time on the
stone bridge, living in darkness. If...  We
don't have a distribution and I'm very worried about this.
I'm really worried because there's so
much of this stuff going on
there, that's why I keep
saying about this book. I'm not
trying to sell books, I'm not trying to post anything.
I don't have a book sales board, but
the world is knitting.  It's in a dark place.
It's like being in a
primitive era, a
primitive night. And if there's a book
about seeds,
it's like sunlight
in this world,
and the assessment is that normally, there's
nothing to say about the light that's always there every day.
How can you mold it? Whether
the sun rises or the sun doesn't mold it.
If there were no living seeds with
this knowledge, this world would be dark,
this world would be in a dark night,
from the primitive nature of the
goddess and the angels. We
just tell you what the world is like. We say,
you say, if we do
normal economic and political things,
normal science things, then
it's really just a superfluous thing.
This world is in a dark era, and
everyone is blind, it's
a dark night, eternally dark, and
everyone is hurting each other.
The news says to register before him.
If we listen to him and
we think that everything comes from
itself and  If we don't
believe that everything is good from
my perspective, like in the kitchen,
then this is really just
dinner time, whether you have internet or not, or
whether you have a phone or not, or whether
you have an airplane or not, or
whether you have a spaceship, you're still
in your
primitive state, and you're killing each other with
Western weapons, silver sticks, and stones.
Oh well,
if we listen to
the truth, then nothing is possible. If
we are the devil, then
everything cannot exist, not just
this world,
not just people hurting
each other. If we follow the
thoughts of that evil devil, then actually
these worlds do
n't even exist. It's not like
this world is carrying bags or there wasn't a time,
not even a primitive dark night.
But if we follow the
thoughts of those devils, that
this world comes from the side that passes
through itself, then there can't be anything.  The Ten-
Mile World is not even as good as the dark world
anymore, there is nothing at all,
the worst thing about the devil is that
they don't understand how bad they are,
they don't even
understand. Yes, the misuse is the lack of clarity,
where does it come from in the systems of
those evil demons,
the evil demons
outside? They don't even understand
where the mistake comes from, they even
misunderstand the misunderstanding.
If I ask them, "Why do
n't you understand this pen?" Ten years
ago, why didn't you understand
this pen? Twenty years ago, and they said, "I
don't know, nobody taught me."
Now you understand the mistake. It's
not that nobody taught you,
but that you didn't share
your knowledge with others,
so you didn't meet anyone who could
teach you. There's a little bit of Facebook gossip, and you
still don't understand why you do
n't understand. You do
n't even understand. How can you
not understand? Le
Thi Quynh
will start getting very annoyed and say that
you
are the whole thing.  This universe,
this entire planet, with its 8
billion people living in small cars, only a
few thousand understand this world.
For a long time, among 8 billion people,
she walked in the darkness, walking
in the darkness. Only a few
people understood the pen,
that pen is the glasses. Your task,
in each country, each nation, your
country,
you must share the story of the pen that
people like to talk about, the story of the
husband left in the kitchen. Try it, it's
very touching, and people say that at
that time, you must remember that it's better
if only one person in
millions understands it.
Wherever it goes,
it will change this world, it will
change the entire balance.
This and the things that begin to
happen will bring more prosperity,
more happiness. Just
one person in a million understands the seed,
and it will accomplish its purpose. In Lam, the
difference is huge in this world
because the mother's thought starts to
spread and spread, right?  I saw the news and there's a
question, right?
We'll have a
Kia Morning tomorrow to
play,
we'll learn a little more, I'll talk about the Q&A
part.
We have another person who likes to
read
a sentence and stand here, we'll go
to Spain,
clip service, only acknowledging verbally the
idea that
ukulele acknowledges verbally the idea
that those things will cause
confusion, but look,
if something is easily confused,
then it also has
its own causes and conditions.
You continue to say instead, those things
can exist without relying on
anything else. You are actually
saying there is no such thing as an
easily confused reality.
Yes, so it
's an idea of ​​breaking the illusion that
can be said tomorrow, a2a,
it's a very
famous idea in Buddhism. They always talk about
Illusion, Illusion, you know.
This is a very super thing,
everyone has wished everyone, I don't understand
why, but which piece of German
is what it is,
sometimes it's called the  Deception and
trickery in Buddhist philosophy
is called filtering, or deception
in Tibetan terms, what is lying? It's
very easy.
Yes, that piece means what? The
dualistic perception says it very correctly:
when you walk into the kitchen and your husband
tells you to do it, right?
Then you don't say anything, you haven't
said anything yet, he just attacks, he
attacks, what will you say? Because he
attacks you, it seems like
he had a bad day,
or he couldn't sleep last night, or he got stuck in
traffic a lot.
He's in a bad mood,
it seems like
the problem is
because he's in a bad mood. In
English, when we say it
seems like that, it's the
deception, and that's it, a a,
there's just an illusion. It seems like
your husband is annoyed today
because something is wrong, it's not
his, it's not the right size, it's not
good, or this guy is his boss,
and that...  This is called deceptive reality,
but what is the truth? The
truth is, last week you yelled at
your child, and you heard those
words, that color, from this to this hand,
and it created a thing, and then it was done,
your main intention, and then it
became a thing like karma. That's
why your husband is
yelling today, it's all your fault.
So what is this deceptive reality?
Thinking that this world is
deceiving you every day,
this world is deceiving you, everyone is
deceiving you. Oh, look at this,
because there's a political problem, that's how it is.
This country is doing this thing,
that country is doing
that thing. I see it,
remember, it's really something. It
could be that you're not friendly with
others, or you're being petty with others,
or your girlfriend is fighting over a lemon tree,
sharing it with others. It creates a
reason. The reason countries are sharing
this is that
we are sharing with others, those people...
Are we friends or people who
love each other? I don't know why
we like each other so much, we haven't seen anyone like it, we
feel unhappy when
others are happy, this is a strange thing.
It seems like the
world
is happening because of all the
forces in this world. But
actually, it's
a boom, it comes from
our side.
Don't think that Buddhism, in the
Buddhists, says that the cup is
not real, look at this,
this iPhone is not real,
don't believe it, don't believe that person, it's not
what the real lines in
Buddhism say, it's not asking if this
is real or if the mobile phone is real. If I
hit you on the head, it will definitely have a
bump on your head,
it's real, but it
really comes to your weak point. It's
not real in the way it
looks.
I will give you a $100
Galaxy to smash and at the same time build with
a phone, and this phone
is you, if you see something with a
bump on top,
smash it.  What is this head part?
Is it coming from the bottom of the phone?
Question 100° Is that thing
coming from the phone? Someone, it's
not
two Ti.
Why, why not? It ca
n't cut it off again. I have to
try something. I have to use something
else. It's not like it's
simple. It seems
crazy.
But if I hit my head,
this top part of my head, with
this mobile phone,
and if the step that appears, that thing does
n't come from the phone, it's
on my head. The phone actually
comes to my seed. The
movement of this phone does
n't. I wake up with my seed, and
then this butterfly, it's
my living seed. But
this hammer, it's not good from what, this mobile phone.
This is very difficult to understand, right?
If I'm having my head with
this mobile phone, and then a
butterfly appears on my head,
this phone comes to live practice.
My
way of moving the phone to get better
from my seeds and then
this meal it also comes from my living things and there is no
connection between
this phone and Google,
no. There can't be any
connection, it's called cause and effect. You
hit something with
this phone, you don't see it today, you see
the sister will come to the Donald Academy, you have to
find out clearly, oh, at the same time there is a gift.
She will take it, so when I turn it on, I hit
my phone, fighting,
then I don't see gashi, that
's not the way to see, I meet this breast tumor.
This phone doesn't
create this thing, it's an illusion.
When these seeds, the seed that
creates the phone, the seed that creates the sword,
and the input seed, it creates the
father and son, the silkworm product, there can't be a connection, the
phone is not connected to the
research, it's not connected to the
mind that hits its head, it's not connected to each other,
each one comes from
different seeds, that's all, interesting.
No, it's all good.
Everything you try to do
to be happier
is a mistake. Everything, everything,
try to drink this watermelon juice
so it doesn't burn, so it doesn't taste bad. That's a
mistake.
You definitely have to give someone else the
juice first, right? Ironing,
right?
Me too? No?
How do I...
Somebody will show an old man, a
baby,
two weeks from now, the baby will grow up. Very
beautiful,
good, right?
I saw a picture, it was beautiful.
Pantene dock,
this is a story about fatherly love.
Congratulations, friends,
I'm on your way to Santa. Here in
Florida,
this is Santa and Jerry Center, Florida.
Appointment schedule, now Mom is a word, three
times again.
Very happy to be here.
In general, we can say that if
we follow the system of selling,
not because nothing can ever die, and
more specifically, we must say that nothing
can ever be born, and now it
is the fact that a Heavenly being has died and
been born as one of
their lesser cousins ​​back when they
had...  The body and mind of a
celestial being looked at those things and said, "
That is me." Now, according to you, when the belief
in a real existence will not change,
and so if now they are looking at the
body and mind of their lesser cousin
and now think it is me, there
will be two, that is me, coming together at
a single place and time.
Of course, that is impossible, but the point
is, it would have to be a necessary result.
With this belief of yours, everything can
exist in truth. So tell me
what will really happen when
those two things come together.
You say, "No, the difficult part, you choose a
really difficult part.
Who likes you? My self, all of you,
when I try to sleep, but I can't
sleep. We will read
this book and will try the important part of
this book, and I will sleep immediately.
It's even better than sleeping pills.
I just need to open this book and try to read
one page. I remember when I was in some
monastery where I was interviewed about sleep.
This book, I will open it, and we will
Trying to move a page
that
helps me fall asleep immediately. I think
in this lineage, in
this tradition,
we cultivate our minds to try to be
rigorous, which promises me many years.
You have to constantly struggle with
what you don't understand, and then
your mind starts to form a group. A
joke about the day to be in the
three-day shift never
has the nature of a commentary on the day of the week. It's
very funny, sad, and funny.
His commentary on ancient books
can't be funny because besides the
salary, the day
is like the easy part for me. I
never have to
write about the roots.
His books give us the part
of the body.
I am very proud to take the book
as the king of the dharmas. It
took 15 years,
but this always ignores the
easy parts, and
we just finish. DJ speed, a
high speed. It talks about
problem-solving, how to solve problems,
and it's like a discipline
that
you should strip. You see your wife at first, then she
turns up, so it's difficult first.  You have to
enjoy it
in this book.
If you don't understand something, or if you're feeling
sleepy, just keep
repeating it. Because there are some
valuable things that, if you understand them
immediately, for example, I can say
it's not a religion. No, it's not
a Bible. It takes
time to understand and pay attention. There's
something that's judged by the
angels and the devils.
If we just keep our system
and everything has a real world outside, it's
just that... It can die,
both or nothing can be born.
Meaning
your car can't break down,
and you can't buy a new one if
the car isn't yours. And
think about this, I'm saying it again.
Yeah,
if your car doesn't come from your ticket,
it will never break down. And if
it doesn't break down, you'll
never be able to buy a new car
if it doesn't come from your side. My friend
Sally and Allison...  I just bought a new car, I
have four, a used car, new
this week,
is there a new car at school? Like
us, we have to say, the reason it's hard to
buy a new car
is because they give others rides, they're
generous
in the past, they help others, even if they
get to the place they need to go, and
I know they really do that, and
this has created the situation where they
get a new car. But if you don't
understand the seed and you think
you can get a new car, then you'll be
crazy. You should... If you
think
you can get a new car
without helping others get to
the place they need to go,
then this is crazy. That's what the
gods say.
Now the angel continues to speak because I see
I'm going to talk about the new car. I am
our body after we
die together, thanks to someone continuing the
conversation, returning
to the things we call the
spirits, right? In the very whisper, I
want the conversation to return.
Initially, when
people talk about
those
who do good things for others,
they don't understand the seed. They
just have a habit of
doing good things, or their mother
tells them to do good things, or their teacher tells them to do
good things, but they don't really understand what
they're doing. They'll still get
good results; their good deeds will go away. For example,
when they die, they might
go to a better place after a
while.
Now, angels talk about
people who
do kind things for others,
but they don't really understand the seed. They
just do kind things
because their mother tells them to, or
their teacher tells them to,
but they don't really understand the seed of
life.
They
'll have a life that's good,
but temporary. They'll burn everything up.
Then, their plans will run
out, and they'll have to learn to die again.
Why would they call it back?  Beautiful reborn in
another place here is
interesting, and when the strange angel
returns, it also has a conversation, when it goes
back to the beginning of the conversation,
and the angel says
what really happened
when you died, then you went to a
new world, what really
happened wasn't that the new world
was waiting for you, wasn't it like
[music]
you send team flags, construction teams
to the world of the new world,
or build a new world for them, then
they invite you, I'm not like that. Down here,
it's good, my fee when I
die, an open world, it comes from my side.
I can't move, you can't
move from one world to
another. I'm just replacing
the world, the last world, with
the new world, with the world where
this world comes from. When you drive to a
grocery store,
you're not going anywhere, it's not
going anywhere. You shouldn't be proactive, and there are
two movements of your mind that create the
world's path.  You create a
little car, you
create a food store from my house,
the food store
sitting in the car,
similar to what you get when you die.
When the end of your life is over,
you enter a new world. You don't enter the new world,
your mind creates the new world and you
enter it. Interesting, right?
Here, the spirit says, "Yes, then you have
things that were lost before.
They accumulated a very long time ago because they
had good seeds,
these seeds were all gone because
they didn't understand seeds.
Then they die, then they enter a
new world. But sometimes they
fall to
a lower speed
because they have used up all
their good seeds.
Only one person remains,
Chi Pu. First, she dies.
She was born in a world
where enemies live, they
become like traps,
like you are a
white person who hates black people,
thinking things like that. Why is that?"
When the plane of madness is something
people won't go to, then the next thing
you'll be born as a black person, are
you hating yourself?
Oh, what happens after that? Is it similar?
I like the Heavenly Master.
First, she
sells the gods. I don't know that it's
as big as your land. You hate a certain country,
then you'll go to your country, we'll be
born in another country, and then
you'll be yourself,
whatever it is, it's already born,
and they're asking here,
our DNA is Peruvian, and you're born in
Argentina,
then it will be concrete, nobody will be you, you'll
go to Peru, into it. You're born in,
when
it really means
your seed, we produce Peru
in 55, 65, 75, then your reaction
changes,
and now the seed starts producing
Argentina, and we say that you're
spirit, you'll go into you, you're born,
but actually it's not like that. It's just
a new seed creating a country.
Next,
and in this appendix, the
new seed of her creates  The seed
of the country you hate is sown, the
seed before
this, so much so, a person hides from
everyone who lives and wants their country in
the resistance of their path,
they learn to hate
other people because they always think about
the people they hate,
that country
in another country.  My cousin, Bang Anh, was born
in a country they hate.
Now the question is,
if you love yourself and hate yourself,
you die in one country and are
born in another. Which one do you
hate?
How much is it? I'm
there, and the angel says, "This one is
starting to get difficult. There
will be two of us here." Why is
one "I am Buddha." I am in Peru. It's real,
not coming from your side, not from the seed.
And I sing "Tina the Bird," it's also real, and
it doesn't come from the seed. So
now, you must be two people. If
you're not in the next life,
if you don't believe in past lives,
if you think, "You might only be born once, not twice," if you think, "
The mistake of being
born only happens once,
not twice," then
there's only one me.
But if the seed is also yours,
creating another you, then which one
is you? Which one is you? Now you
don't need to believe
in past lives yet.  Before or after, forget everything,
forget past and future lives, no need to
worry about
bad luck. I don't accept the concept of what
comes after tomorrow, that's probably okay. Do
you accept tomorrow? Do you
accept that you will be here tomorrow? Oh,
so this person is trying to find something,
the person of tomorrow
comes from the person of today,
the person of tomorrow comes
from the person of today,
and we say that it comes from like
that. If you see something from there, a seed, a
sitting. And if the person of
today comes from a seed,
then the person of tomorrow comes from a seed, is that
possible? Then the seed. If in change
and the nurturing of today
becomes the sitting of tomorrow, if that's the case,
why? Now it's not. If
it can't be like that,
then it's just the nature of today,
and then there's a person of tomorrow,
another person of tomorrow who likes this,
which one is you
if it's not a seed. If
from a seed that doesn't produce
today is today, and the seed is
not  I like to create tomorrow,
and if I open myself up today, it's
not really me coming from a seed,
and if I tomorrow am really me, not me coming
from a seed,
then which one is me? What is my
true self? What is my strong self
today? I still have tomorrow, which one is to
report?
We say that we
can only move from today
to tomorrow when the seed changes.
When the seed gives birth to tomorrow, when the seed of tomorrow gives birth to
what is tomorrow, then the seed of tomorrow,
yesterday, it ends, then you
can move from today to
tomorrow. There will be no other person,
no other person at
all. That's how we move from
today to tomorrow. We
can say, "Ah,
after studying, then it will go to the
academy, about 40 minutes drive." With
this thought,
my seed creates my house, and
my living seed creates the work that Mr.
Michael is sitting in the house, and
those customers are finished.
And then the new seed creates the car, and the
new seed creates the world, the next room,
and after.  That new seed created the
university, and then that
new seed created the time when Michael was sitting
in the university. That's how
Michael went to the university. Michael
didn't get in the car and drive to the
university
in 15 minutes. It's like that,
so it's not real. It's
not real. The
seed created Michael
sitting at home. The seed created Michael
driving, and the seed
created Michael in the university.
That's when I saw Michael going to the
university. If I don't have ancestors, parents, I wo
n't have to give the cat anything,
okay?
We'll go to
Facebook in the Q&A
section because the next part is
quite difficult.
I'll go back to part 2 later.
Some people asked this question
recently, and I'll summarize it. The
person who wanted this flower answered, "I have my
own seed, and
everything comes to my essence." And it seems
like other people out there
also have their own seeds; they
also have their own experiences.  They
suffer in their own way, it
seems like they... My sister said that the karmic consequences
that are being experienced are different from my child's,
but when I say that all of
this comes, it also comes with a price from my
child, that karma. So
how do we think about it again?
Because it seems
like not everyone
has their own seeds,
and all of that is not good from
my child's perspective. How do we think about
this?
This year I am 69 years old.
I have been worried. Is this something that can be obtained in 50
years? Why am I
teaching this class? All the questions
you are asking, I also have
those questions down here,
and this is a great question, and I am
also very surprised by this question. It
means I am lucky because I was not
born a dead thing, I was not born
in mud.
There is nothing to say about Buddhism coming from
my parents, my two countries,
or my culture, all of it.
My physics knowledge comes from
my teacher and from great books,
and
I have all the questions that you guys
have ever asked, like that question,
similar questions, I've struggled with this question for many
years.
I like to think of it as all of it. Tuan is a
big ball,
like the one I'm
creating now. I see the
mountains, I see the sky.
I live in a mountainous region.
I'm seeing the whole
desert, there are mountains, and the blue sky.
That's my ball. It comes from
my living particle.
Then you also have your own ball.
You have a ball in Florida,
your own creation. It creates Florida around you. There's
no
ball like that. I've created it. I have a ball about stars, and
then I like to think of
it as a man traveling in
space with a helmet.
Recently I read about a
Garena night, a
famous Russian cosmologist, his
helmet, the
first helmet, the
first helmet in space.  Yeah, from
Soviet imagination, I think
this is great, like those
scientists in Russia who
invented the helmet, the red helmet that dances in space,
and everyone, the ability to use it, you can
think about your living seed
blooming and creating a helmet
in space, your own powerful one,
like a virtual universe, I'm in
virtual reality. Sometimes you can talk to
another person and you two helmets
touch each other, two astronaut foam pieces
touch each other, a bubble,
a brush into my bubble,
when the place where they touch,
we all have a conversational particle like yours
creating words and my seed
creating words, and
we will be able to have communication
and interaction, meaning
from
your seed creating words
and my seed creating
sounds
to hear your words at the same
time, the
helmet is ours, or
our bubbles, they fit
together, then you can see the Galaxy.  Speaking on
rum and you can ask questions on
rum,
you can think of ways like that and that's
right, this way is quite correct.
There is a
beautiful form of spiritual practice that you can practice. It
is a tradition. It is an
Asian tradition of Asia.
Let's try to understand
that maybe the people around you...
Don't have completely different bubble results
of a moment. Sometimes you
sit down by the sound. Thinking without exercising
without needing to know, you
can talk to another person.
You can even enjoy breakfast
together,
but you don't try to know
how they are experiencing this world.
And after the tradition, there is a
village tradition. We will have a
special money bone during the
day. Just imagine
that those other people are
completely clearing their seeds.
The people around you.
They are seeing
heaven. Your kind
is like that. A normal life,
a normal world. Maybe the
person sitting next to you is a
president next year with a hat, with a
different bubble.  It's completely different. It's absolutely
certain that there must be some people in
this world
whose teachings have existed for
2,500 years—that's 100 generations of books. The
book that the team just completed...
how is it that in the past 100 generations,
from 2,500 years ago,
people didn't keep these books and
they didn't pass them on
to the next generation if it was
n't effective, if it wasn't useful.
This book would have died long
ago. This is the lonely blame. Which book is
ineffective? It would have died long ago.
If a book were still alive,
this is the book by Nam Kim K, it could be in
your hand. If this book is still
in
2050, it means it has helped someone,
someone has translated this book,
someone has republished it, and
you, Red Star, we create books on
Facebook.
If this book
survives in this world
for 2,500 years,
it will certainly be effective
for someone.  That has an effect on someone.
Certainly, there are people in this world who
have finished and will be in their heaven, and
their seeds have been
sown, producing
a heaven. There must
be such people,
and their bubbles are certainly different.
Regarding the bubbles of my uncle, there was
someone who asked my teacher, I
remember it was in many places, it's called a number,
or it has a question. My teacher asked
if it
's something that happens, that
we create things together, that we
create a perfect life, at the same
time, has it ever happened in the
future like that, that
everyone's space helmet is the
same, and we are all
sharing the same world, the
same empty space,
and the teacher said that it is true, that is the
Mandala, it is
called a perfect world. When you
teach, you also have a bed, and it's a la, right?
When you make offerings, it's called a leaf. Does that
mean that at
some point,
everyone's helmet...  It's okay, people are all the
same, and we get to see
each other. Those are the Buddhas, and I will never
forget the last word. I saw them
say, or rather, they said,
what happened. All of us...
I don't know what the remote teacher said. What
happens next? It
means what will happen next. I said, "
I don't know, teacher," but in my heart...
those relics... they only retire. They only
think about it, like about the Buddha. They have retired.
You have your paradise, right? I have
my paradise. We create
similar paths and see it. What do you
think? They all
rest. And they say it doesn't seem like it's an equation.
This Buddha isn't retired, and they see it's right.
The teacher said
they're just having fun together, they're just
enjoying
that bubble together. Together they
don't look at each other. I asked the woman, "Just having fun,
giving each other that is the future.
The path, right?
Grandpa has to go teach another class, right?